hello and welcome to DC podcast I'm Eric
dick today we're talking customer
support with a brand leader who
supported a lot of customers potentially
the most customers of any DC apparel
brand in the past 5 years we're talking
true classic the T-shirt giant who
reported a quarter of a billion dollars
over their first four years last year
today Brianna Moreno customer support
Maverick and VP of CX a true classic
gives us the breakdown of the system
she's built to support the incredibly
fast-paced growth that they've
experienced there while actively turning
her division into a profit Center
Brianna is a true classic herself and
literally the company's first official
hire beyond the founders so she's been
there for the whole Wild Ride listen in
and you'll get Brianna's insights on
support as a sales channel for upselling
and cross- selling how to harness
support data and interactions to fuel
effective marketing and product
development as well as how and why you
should be integrating your support with
your customer retention and loyalty
programs I hope you enjoy this one on
with the show I just excited to really
challenge myself on how can we leverage
AI how can we get to understand it
better is this a tool that's going to
work where is this going to take us we
implemented an AI help death solution
last year we saw phenomenal results both
from an acquisition standpoint and a
retention standpoint we're seeing like
conversion just significantly increase I
think we saw over 3 million and
increased Revenue just from our support
team everybody in the CX space knows Q4
is generally when you're going to have
to staff up right you're going to have
to bring in extra resources you're
generally going to have a backlog
meaning you're not burning through your
tickets as much it's going to take you
longer and we saw none of
that content from real people equals
instant credibility for your brand
consumers today crave real connections
with real people and they're guarded
about who they'll trust highly polished
branded content simply doesn't cut it
anymore let Min social build a network
of powerful micro influencers around
your brand who all know and love your
products they'll create something
compelling that resonates With Their
audience and deliver it directly to you
for use across all your marketing
channels yeah that includes ads meet
Millennials and Jen zers where they're
already hanging out in the feeds of
their favorite influencers and get
started with Min
social Brianna Welcome to the Toc
podcast I am really happy to have you
here can you start us off by giving us a
little bit of a rundown of your your
hero's journey and how you became uh
where where you're at today yeah it's
not really exciting I wish I had some
amazing story to tell but I I don't um I
got actually into the new home building
industry while I was still in college
worked in Corporate America I was really
young so it took twice the amount of
everybody else for me to really create a
name and stake for myself during the
market crash in
2009 I was presented an opportunity and
I was so grateful um as we Consolidated
the business I was able to work with one
of my mentors that I had just absolutely
admired for so long and really learned
the value of getting more done with less
and I think that's what's what's stuck
with me to this day I stayed in the new
home building industry probably a good
12 to 14 years when I was pregnant with
my third child uh the company relocated
and I was just not willing to have three
young kids in daycare in a really Hefty
commute so I decided to try the
stay-at-home mom thing which I proved to
not be very well at because I kind of
loved that aspect of me time and and
really the challenge of work and and all
of that so I decided to look at what I
could do from home and and I was a
consumer of a product called chatbooks
they're automated photo books and loved
journaling so it kind of went hand inand
and I started to work in their customer
support team quickly scaled with them
obviously I was probably a little bit
overqualified but again it was just fun
and I was looking for Challenge and I
was working with one of the co-founders
on potentially moving over into coding
because again I just thrive on challenge
and I want to continue to grow and I was
presented by the CEOs and told that they
had a friend of theirs in the business
that was looking for somebody to grow
and scale their CX team and from there I
moved over to Freshly picked built and
scaled their CX team had an amazing time
building that company and then Nick
Ventura from True classic found me I
think probably on LinkedIn or something
and connected with them and then
inevitably made the choice to leap over
to classic and work with the guys hand
inand on on building CX for them so fun
fact is I was actually employee number
one at true classic wow what are they at
approximately now what are you at
approximately now as a whole
organization oh my gosh we're well over
50 probably I would say 75 maybe I don't
know I haven't we just had another
hiring span um fun fact again this week
we're doing our company All Hands we do
our qbr meeting so I'm actually going
into the office tomorrow um we have some
of our international team visiting so
it's always so fun to get FaceTime but
yeah I we're pro we've got to be I would
say between 60 to 70 now maybe very cool
um on this podcast we talk all the time
about you know uh we're an agency and so
we talk about ads a lot we talk about
growth a lot U when I when I reached out
to you about about uh coming on the
podcast you were really eager to speak
about customer support about CX what
what do you feel about like today's
e-commerce climate and how hyper
relevant CX is versus maybe things like
ads and growth specifically today such a
good
question um I think inevitably so much
of our industry is focused on marketing
and initiatives of acquisition right
retention but at the end of the day I
always find Value in that first touch
point with a brand that human touch
point that human element which is
generally the support team um it's
something that I'm super passionate
about and and very proud of because we
really have the ability to sway that
consumer from you know converting or
from staying when something goes wrong
right so whether it be like in our world
maybe they need help with sizing or in
previous worlds you know we would help
with pairing of product of of whether
you know we're working on a mom brand or
a kids brand and you yourself are a mom
you can obviously give really good
insights on styling or experience and
really the ability to connect with your
consumer I think is what sets CX apart
love it I think marketing's job is often
to kind of get that first purchase in a
lot of ways but what's so important for
for Brands to thrive and for Brands to
grow the way that true classic has you
need to be optimizing down the line to
the second third fourth purchase I I am
a ongoing purchaser of true classic it's
funny my duplex uh neighbor beside me
I'm constantly seeing true classic
packages coming to his house so you're
doing a good job of getting people to
make more than one purchase in an
ongoing fashion which is probably just
absolutely critical to your meteoric
growth that you've had yes yes and that
is again I think with ads you see so
often people are like is there a real
company behind this is this a shell
company I don't know if you've purchased
from companies before and you like never
get your product shipped
I'm part of that I get it I understand
and I think that's where the support
team can really make a difference it's
not just about you know the support team
on the other end that's that's working
to try to get somebody to convert right
or maybe they're working to mitigate
something that went wrong but at the end
of the day it's about that human element
which I think is is why I love
leveraging our support that feedback the
Data Insights that they get generally 9
% of the time our support team is going
to know whether something is a good idea
or not because they just know our our
consumers better than anybody I mean
they're talking to them day in and day
out so I think again that's just
something that I'm I'm so proud of is
it's not just about what we're selling
at true classic but more about the
community that we're building and and
we're more than willing to work to earn
trust because we understand in the e-com
space either there's a ton of other you
know people in the market it's maybe
it's saturated but there has to be a
reason why you're purchasing from a
brand and and to come back and time and
time again we may get influenced right
and like oh okay I'm going to get this
because I saw it on whatever um but then
there's a different element to actually
connecting with the brand and that's
something that I'm so proud of what
we've built here and um certainly makes
it easier when you have Founders that
are are definitely just as passionate
about giving back about creating a sense
of community about doing the right thing
even you know in an instance where maybe
the the customer clicked the wrong thing
like it doesn't matter we're going to
fix it no matter what because we want
you to trust us and we want you to feel
that you know this is an inclusive space
for you so excited that your neighbor
knows about us and is is continuously
purchasing from us that's that's such an
honor and it it's also you know to bring
it to ads as well which is where my mind
always goes a lot of the best
advertising and is is in so often
informed by that human side of things
like you can learn so much about the
angles that you're talking about in your
ads or or you're sending in your emails
from these these human interactions that
you have on the support side do you guys
do a I I imagine you do but you do a
good job connecting those you know those
instances that happen Ono one with with
customer support through back to the
whole marketing funnel yeah oh my gosh I
can't tell you how many times like we've
taken actual feedback from our
consumers and use that in paid or just
any type of marketing leverage because
it's like look this is real life and and
I think that's such a huge aspect of
earning trust right and showing that
you're a real company and there's real
people behind that but yeah we we love
we have a a membership group in uh
Facebook and this has just been so fun
getting to know them more so on like a
personal level and um getting in there
and just engaging with them but we have
some really great stories of people
coming to us and sharing their story or
their experience with true classic
that's kind of like over the toop that
we've we've asked like hey we would love
to use this in a campaign or we'd love
to share your feedback um that's always
fun and it and it really you know
connects us with them just as much as um
them with us kind of thing very cool
what is your team look like at this
point I've talked I when I've talked to
CX leaders in the past there's we're
really having a moment right now with AI
and the tools that are available on the
support side of things so talk about
what your team looks like and whether
has it has it been has it been getting
bigger is it getting smaller with AI and
then how do you view the AI as a tool in
this process such a good question um I
think AI is a buzz word we've seen it
since last year that's actually when I
decided to really challenge myself on
how can we leverage AI how can we get to
understand it better you know is this a
tool that it's going to work where is
this going to take us um I met such such
amazing brands that are actually leading
Ai and that have been like building it
and leading it for years prior to us
even pulling our stuff together to even
look at it um but yeah we we implemented
an AI help desk solution last year we
saw phenomenal results like amazing both
from an acquisition standpoint and a
retention standpoint we're seeing like
conversion just significantly increase I
think they did a case study and it was
you know we saw over 3 million in
increased Revenue just from our support
team it it it was amazing to see and I
think again everybody in the CX space
knows Q4 is generally when you're going
to have to staff up right you're going
to have to bring in extra resources
you're generally going to have a backlog
meaning you're not burning through your
tickets as much it's going to take you
longer and we saw none of that this year
we scaled down in our support team quite
significantly um obviously we cut cost
which was really interesting but
leveraging these these automation tools
it's really cool because a lot of them
won't charge you unless they fully
automate uh so that's that's really
interesting and I learned so much in the
difference between Automation and true
AI where it's coming in and solving the
problem either partially which cut down
you know your resolution times or it's
fully deflecting meaning you know
customers email or chat never even
touched a live agent it was just living
with AI the whole time and still one of
the things that was so important to me
was I didn't want to sacrifice seat for
that so allowing us to still measure
like a 94% seat across deflection again
no agents involved to me was a win I am
willing to assume the risk on such a
small percentage if again the costs and
the benefits are so much greater um and
we saw this again even like through our
returns portal post purchase like being
able to leverage AI there for our
previous we were with a previous vendor
having challenges from a Global
Perspective AI really came in helped us
solve for that so a strong proponent
definitely of the mindset that it
doesn't get it right all the time which
neither do humans um but it really did
shift my mindset even even uh using AI
on phones uh was something just
mindblowing again to see the decrease in
cost and increase in customer experience
it really proves the point of people are
responding really well to this if you do
it right and that's what we're
challenging ourselves with is making
sure we're doing it right we're not
adding frustration but we are leveraging
um the tools that are out there and then
to follow up with that because it's
freed up so much of our agent time that
then allows them to have more impactful
conversation we could do proactive
messaging with a live agent you know
from like a stylus perspective a
marketing perspective having live
conversation and engagement or you know
troubleshooting whatever type of issues
you're running into it allows them to be
more intentional in those instead of
having to move so quickly to solve for
everything and then practically with
with AI when when the customer is
engaging it are they in your system are
they aware it's are you sort of like hi
I'm a I'm an AI bot here to help you or
is it sort of like one seamless process
how do you go about identifying what's
Ai and what's not yeah it's one I don't
want people to know that it's AI off the
bat most of them do in the current state
we're in right now a ton of testing last
year that we we're doing to really
understand how are people responding to
it but I don't want to come out and say
hey we're a bot because I think it just
automatically puts up a guard um so
we're testing we're testing so many
different aspects of it um obviously
from generative AI perspective we're
using zi so in their solution so it's
less risk than like an open AI That's
just God only knows what it's going to
say hallucinating yeah yeah yeah I trust
in their their offer their system
they've like I said been building this
for years but again we're testing seeing
what works seeing what consumers respond
to and again there's so much I don't
think people realize how much effort is
put into to training an AI that to me
this may be an automated response but
it's not 100% without a human we are
absolutely teaching it enabling it uh
monitoring it growing it so there's so
much effort put into the AI that I don't
want people to think this is just a bot
um it really is a personality and and
we're working on building that right now
so I kind of leave it up and and it
there is there's generally a handoff and
you you don't really know is this a
human or not and that's the element of
surprise that I want to I want to keep
cuz it it doesn't matter whether it's a
bot or a human we need to solve your
problem as quickly and as painlessly as
we can and that's the goal and ideally
you want to create a a web experience
that is so clear or so intuitive that
you don't even get to that point where
support is necessary you want your
marketing message and your product to be
so aligned that you you know the best
customer supporters is what you don't
even hear about because they solved it
all themselves I guess right yeah yeah
true like proactive messaging of course
setting expectations um you know those P
post-p purchase flows we've seen such an
increase in that and making more
intentional interactions again like I
said with our Global markets you know
you're missing the beat there and
setting expectation then you're right if
you do not set clear expectation then
it's going to lead to friction it's
going to lead to people popping over and
saying what the heck's going on with my
order um you know it's been X amount of
time we know people don't read so it is
such an art to try to set clear
expectation on your website making sure
that you're giving them as much insight
as possible without overloading them but
but 100% that is always the goal and and
we've seen a significant decrease in our
ticket to order ratio by just like you
said proactively solving something
before it becomes an issue you mentioned
cessat and I love new acronyms I I I can
add a new acronym every every time I do
a podcast that's a big win uh customer
satisfaction how do you actually measure
customer satisfaction practically so
everybody that we talk to on every
channel is given a seat request so we
send them a survey that just says hey
how would you rate the interaction you
had with your support agent and that is
where they'll give like a one to five
star rating and then they can leave
comments again we do the same thing even
if it's automated or with a live agent
because I want to know from that
consumer not just how would you rate it
but is there feedback is there somewhere
that we fell short is there something we
need to improve we do this on the phone
lines too that are also automated uh so
again any feedback my perception is any
feedback is good feedback positive or
negative obviously to help us increase
but the good news is we run about a 98%
Collective uh seat which ISE freaking
amazing amazing in our industry and
something that I'm so proud of super
cool and you mentioned it earlier just
being able to isolate the fact that I
think you said three million of of um
additional sales kind of made through
this customer support Channel talk you
know everyone the buzzword on the
marketing side is is profitable
marketing you we used to call it
Performance Marketing the big buzzword
these days is is just really making sure
that you're profitable from your first
dollar spent in marketing if you can
talk about profitable customer support
and how you measure that and how like
cuz I know there's all sorts of there's
there's tools there's sort of like sales
concierges you mentioned stylists where
youve got that ability to say hey you
might like this this this pants with
this shirt kind of thing talk about how
you think about profitable customer
support yeah I look at I mean our
conversion alone you know we put every
company out there put so much money and
effort to their site right you want it
to perform you want it to convert but
the reality is if you look at the your
site conversion compared to your support
conversion you're going to see a vast
difference in there which is great
because if you did not have that support
team imagine how much lower your site
conversion would be so we look at a ton
of things but one of them is our
conversion how valuable are we as
support agents to be able to either
convert firsttime customers returning
customers or retain customers after
something's gone wrong let's say there
was a mishap with their delivery right
they could essentially kind of lose
trust on us and and and be a little
leery and upset so it's up to us to make
sure we're utilizing all of our our
trained skills to ensure that that
customer is coming back time and time
again and we have significant
significant impact there as well so we
look at from a cost perspective I look
at like a cost per ticket which we break
down by all of our hard costs and then I
don't even take into account that
Revenue but I could tell you it's it's a
no-brainer it's so easy to see how low
our cost per ticket is and that's
essentially saying we are Beyond
efficient we're Beyond efficient which
means we can automate a significant
amount of tickets and then leverage our
team to then sell to these consumers or
fix problems with these consumers that
are going to result in them coming back
time and time again all of that we're
doing so efficiently that we have such a
low cost per ticket I talked to many
vendors who don't believe me on it and I
have to show them our cost per ticket is
is like staggeringly low and that comes
from a process standpoint you have to be
good you have to know your costs in
order to kind of fall that low but at
the end of the day for our team I'm
really giving them a platform to show
their value and and that's how we're
doing it across seat across our cost per
ticket across our LTD we're generating
like a 34% % higher LTV than just
customers that don't correspond with
support so that's again we have a higher
conversion rate we're at like a 14%
conversion rate versus our site
conversion rate we have a higher LTV
which means these consumers are spending
more after conversing with our support
team and and mind you these are very
like low Windows we're looking at 72
hours that's what we're capturing but
again these are all aspects of value
that are driven by a support team which
I think often goes unnoticed right like
people just tend to look at it as a cost
center it's just a a necessity an
operational need an operational cost but
the reality is if you're doing it well
it can mean more profit than anything
you've ever seen before and you're doing
all of this Innovation on on the support
side amidst one of the like the fastest
growing like apparel brands in the world
I think that you know you're reducing
your team size which is pretty crazy to
do all of this amidst like the
incredible growth trajectory that true
classic has had it's got to be pretty
pretty Breakneck like talk a little bit
about that experience of sort of
innovating within such a crazy high
growth environment you know it really
starts with the team it really starts
with like that foundational build of
like look here's where we're going uh
some of the girls had followed me from
Brands prior and that's kind of like the
conversation that we had initially right
off the bat is this is going to be a
wild ride this company has the ability
to just soar and we get to be part of it
so the sky is the limit and these these
team players are so insanely good at
what they do that they're not afraid
they're not afraid to take their risks
they're not afraid to take the leap uh
we're all in it together we support each
other when you know when challenges
arise like we have each other to bounce
ideas off of but at the end of the day
we look back at the things that we just
can't even fa them and we're already
here right and it's like going on year
four for me and I still have the same
team so like yes support has scaled but
our internal team that kind of does all
the backend process builds and and
managing of the day-to-day is still the
same size as when we started back in
2020 which is mind-blowing and then can
you share any insights for how you've
kind of kept that team really motivated
and you know driven to to succeed and
just I I imagine it's a department that
quite often would have a fair amount of
turnover uh it sounds like you've had
very little talk a little bit about how
you built this team out and how you
incentivize and inspire people yeah I
think I think that's a great word is
inspire people um like I said the sky's
the limit right so my goal as a leader
here in the industry is to help
everybody get to that next level of
where they're headed and where they want
to go really trying to empower people to
be thoughtful Forward Thinking ERS right
we we want to be thought leaders in our
industry and our space we want to
constantly be three four five steps
ahead because again from a support
perspective we always have to be fluid
right we always have to be agile we're
going to be cleaning up problems that we
didn't necessarily create but at the end
of the day like you can't stop and
complain about it you can't stop and and
be fearful of it we have to adapt we
have to already have a solution before a
problem arises and I think having that
mentality and having that space enables
you to accept that throughout the entire
organization so as the organization
grows and scales at a rapid
Pace it's easy for us to adapt it's easy
for us to be agile because we're already
accustomed to that it's like in our
blood and I think again how you get to
that space is making sure that you have
a platform for people to give feedback
you know you have these working sessions
where you're kind of bouncing off ideas
off of each other you're you're being
mindful of the industry and and what's
happening and what's changing um you're
you're sort of defensive over what
you've accomplish and and the
Partnerships that you've built because
you've put so much heart and soul into
it and I think you're only able to
achieve that with a really strong team I
have this analogy that I I used to do
when I would do team calls but it's like
we're all in a boat rowing right and we
all have to be I mean if you've ever
seen rowing it's like a freaking art
where they're just rowing like and you
think how the hell somebody messes up
and that boat's you know going to soar
left and I I tell the team like we all
have to do our part in rowing and the
minute somebody stops you're dragging us
down or you're deflecting our direction
of where we're going and so I think
again collectively we have such a great
culture we have such great relationships
we've built this together that everybody
literally does this rowing seamlessly
and it it really is magic so that's the
human side and then from the technical
side growing as fast as you have can you
give an example of how you've kind of
leveraged customized solutions to help
true Classics customer support needs
this is my favorite thing ever and I'm
so passionate about this and sometimes
people laugh at me and they're like are
you on their pay roll and I'm like no
but this is a big freaking deal because
we've all worked so hard to make
solutions that are not out there and so
when you finally get to like check that
box you're like hella of excited so we
let leverage these Partnerships and we
build really strong relationships with
them and they in turn support us right
and they make these amazing builds to
solve for problems that we're facing as
a brand which I I think more people are
in Industry need to think about like the
out-of-the-box solution is great for so
and so but what about you what about
your business and we saw this so much so
when we expanded internationally people
just were not supporting the
international side so so really
partnering with amazing vendors that are
solving a need for us with a custom
build allows us to do things that are
just not on the market like again the AI
automation we're doing with zoi the
Integrations that they've built the fact
that my support team never once pops out
of their help desk is unheard of I mean
you could talk to Brands and they're
like yeah 30 to 40% of the agent time is
spent popping into various different
solutions and we saw for that because I
knew it was going to drive down costs it
was going to drive up efficiencies you
know we we partnered with parcel lab
last year to build a AI solution for an
estimated delivery date that's like not
a guarantee but again like we talked
about earlier setting that expectation
giving people clear expectation we
couldn't we couldn't solve that with
these other vendors and they came up
with a solution we built an amazing
return platform with them they built a
custom solution for us with quality
issues so this automates it for the
support agent to where they're not
having to do replacement orders it's all
automated drills down into the data so
specific that we can then Offset you
know potential credits or or issues with
manufacturing or with fulfillment like
again just these custom solutions that
make your life so much easier and limit
your cost that's value that's
profitability and at the same time now
we're helping these vendors build a
better solution that they can in turn
offer to the rest of the industry so
it's a win-win for everybody for sure I
imagine yeah it's it like when when you
guys you guys are a big dog basically
and you're able to go into these
situations I bet it's a challenge at
times for for these Brands to build up
custom Solutions but they end up much
better for it on the other side because
they've sort of had everything sort of
Tried by fire uh in the true classic
experience yes yes and and working like
often times they'll bring in like the C
or co-founders because they want to
learn they want to learn what's in our
brain what we're thinking because that
allows them to build a better solution
for their customers I I'm actually going
to do a podcast um with your VP
marketing I think coming up soon and I'm
I remember like just the you know all
brands in 2024 have to have a really
strong narrative or a really strong
story in order to connect through and
and and build that great brand and I
remember you know just the essential
story of true classic going into a
pretty fairly commod space or very a
very uh competitive space of of apparel
and just to be able to have this
Narrative of like okay our shirts fit
you better um our shirts fit better
around the arms around the waist what's
the importance of having that story
through to the customer support side I
guess you just really need to be able to
deliver and make sure that your your
agents and that your AI is sort of
echoing the story that's kind of
delivered on the front end that's such a
good perspective is like people really
need to make sure that they align on
their brand guidelines right that that
brand tone the brand Persona because
that's going to create cohesiveness
throughout every touch point which I
think we're really good so whether you
talk to somebody online you get an email
from us or you visit one of our retail
locations we want that experience to all
be cohesive with our brand tone and you
you get our Vibe you you'll see this a
lot like in our ads we we love to tap
into humor because humor just makes
everybody feel good and that's again
started with Ryan our CEO it really
resonates with him he does things like
this all the time like earlier this year
it was you know uh doing the teachers
wish lists we're constantly looking for
surprise and Delight moments with our
actual customers or just people in
general so it it it starts there where
it's a real human perspective we we make
fun of ourselves sometimes but it's it's
all in good fun and I think that's what
sets us apart um people know our name it
was amazing in Vegas last week just how
many people were like oh my gosh true
classic oh I love your teas and just
random conversations um that if my son
had some friends over this weekend and
one of the kids was telling my husband
that him and his dad are huge true
classic fans and it's just funny because
it's like wow they they know our brand
and it's like you put so much effort and
care and intention into it so when you
see or hear of these stories on the flip
side it really is so kind of like
humbling and knowing like okay okay
we're doing a good job it's like when
your kids behave at their friend's house
and the mom tells you oh my gosh your
kid's such an angel and you're like
thank God they were an angel right
you're like okay they sa their best for
when they're outside the house usually
right I'll take it yeah I'll take it you
guys innovate across every we were just
talking about shop talk and I the last
conference I was at where true classic
was there you have your poker chips
these these uh the poker chips with uh
you know prod even even when it comes to
your appearances at trade shows you're
innovating for surprise and delight and
I bet I I saw Ryan posting on LinkedIn
with his you know a big handful of these
poker chips I bet you probably had a
bunch of people kind of coming up to you
just looking for that that Innovation
yeah I never did get to connect with him
I was going to steal some and I would
have like dropped him off of a balcony
but um I did bring my own and it was it
was so awesome because whether you know
I there was hardly anybody I had talked
to that hadn't already known about our
brand um and we're actively purchasing
we have this guy from parcel lab who had
no clue never met him before but he's
actually in our membership group and
giving us valuable feedback on the
product and telling us how much he loves
it and um so getting to see them face to
face it's so fun but we we did Ryan
originally designed those poker chips
for poker go I think it was a promotion
we had done um he obviously is a you
know expressional poker player so um it
was so fitting I brought them last year
to to shop talk cuz I thought this makes
such perfect sense and then um got some
more this year and I know I'm sure Ryan
gave a ton out but but definitely just
wanting to like like you said you know
sprinkle some surprise and Delight
everywhere we go any other take I
haven't been to shop talk I really I'm
going to make it a priority to I think
get there next year any big takeaways
from from this year at shop talk you
know I think the big takeaway was just
Community seeing everybody come together
and innovate on things that you know we
haven't seen in our industry um it's
it's really a sense of of community and
and learning kind of like educating
ourselves on you know different aspects
of the business or the industry that
maybe we don't we don't have all the
insights for but seeing everybody come
together was probably one of the best
things ever they definitely know how to
party these these people are a good time
I could not keep up with them definitely
make sure you get your rest before cuz
it is exhausting it's very
overwhelming the the size I heard it's
supposed to be even bigger next year
which I have no clue how they're going
to strategically pull that off but um so
next year will definitely be a good year
for you to test it out but just um you
know load up on your vitamins beforehand
and go into it very open-minded it's
hard to do it all you cannot do it all
you cannot see it all but you will have
these really cool moments where you just
connect with community and that's what
makes it worth it what was your mission
kind of going into it was it really just
to kind of connect with with your fans
connect connect with with other people
in the industry who support or did you
have specific sort of objectives to to
what you wanted to do at at chop talk no
I went into it you know going in and
supporting the vendors that I work with
zoi and parcel being there as a leverage
for them to just share my story with
fellow Merchants out there that that may
or may not be going across the same the
same challenges um so I really didn't
have any expectations but what I got
from it was meeting people that have
been following my journey unbeknownst to
me being able to just connect with them
and have a conversation and it being so
impactful to them is so humbling to me
like I'm I'm just a person I'm just
doing what I do and the fact that that
you know encourages other people is is
such a blessing and an honor and it was
such an amazing opportunity to connect
with them and to sit down and have lunch
and I'm an open book so I share ideas
and and again thoughts Forward Thinking
ideas and and suggestions and I think
that resonates with people um it's hard
in in my space to find I didn't have a
predecessor I didn't learn from anybody
I'm I'm really self-taught trial and
error and so trying to be that for
somebody else makes it all worth it for
myself personally you mentioned going
global and I think true classic is
probably Going Global in a way that a
lot that a lot of the brands I haven't
touched or I've talked to haven't
haven't kind of beg to to tackle what
does what does your Global like approach
look like is it truly it like what are
your biggest markets outside of North
America I would say yeah North America's
one of them um Australia New Zealand
Europe those are strong ones we're
seeing Mexico
surprisingly really well performing
really well on volume um obviously we
went big like true classic we said let's
test them all let's see who responds um
we we opened some local fulfillment
centers at the Q4 of last year which
again is is unheard of we've recently
revamp or not revamped but just scaled
our international team so we've got some
amazing players that are helping us just
really dive in and perfect that whole
aspect of the business and we're seeing
we're seeing the benefits and and the
growth on that side
this is something for me personally that
I'm really excited about is just working
to understand Global markets and and
what is the expectation by region of
shopping for them and and you know what
are the expectations that they predict
that they'll have with the brand and
then I want to come in and obviously
exceed those expectations and so I'm
looking forward to doing that this year
really diving into the international
consumer side of things and and better
understanding that so again we can be
wherever they need us to be and we can
earn that trust and and build community
is this all happening in English or does
your site translate into Spanish and any
any other place that you might be
tackling yeah we do have some um local
language translation on our site so
whether it be France or we haven't yet
gone to Spanish but we're working on it
um but yes we we do have translated
sites already very well underway and
then again if you happen to convert with
the support side that's all translated
automated as well I just feel like we're
in a in a Renaissance of Americana is is
whether it's it's latent right now I
think it'll be coming in in the next few
years and I feel like there's nothing
more American than the than the white
T-shirt with with a pair of jeans so I
feel like there just a huge opportunity
to kind of grow the brand
internationally on the back of a
renissance of Americana yes yes and to
see kind of like you know what do they
love the most and it it is interesting
kind of to see the similarities like you
know our staple sixpack is a favorite
for everybody but yeah it's it's we are
not just a US business anymore by any
means like we are 100% Global both from
our team perspective and just just
everything in between and it it really
is exciting to watch um you mentioned
not having you know that you're kind of
figuring this out as you go as a c CX
leader and Advocate if if anyone in the
is listening in the podcast who wants to
kind of innovate like you have in CX
where would you recommend they kind of
follow your journey or or potentially
even reach out yeah they can definitely
reach out to me I've done so many
different mentorship kind of
consultations with with different
Merchants out there and just organic
conversation definitely get a hold of me
probably linkedin's the easiest way to
to track me down and yeah I know I I
wish there was this I wish there was a
book that I could put it all in because
there's so much to to kind of put you
know pen to paper and and really like a
checklist but happy to be a resource for
anybody out there that's that's going
through challenges or just want to learn
more um it's definitely exciting all
right well I await your book because I
think you definitely could write one I
think that's a great idea but yeah
thanks so much for coming on the podcast
today Brian this is great thank you such
an honor so much fun and um maybe I'll
be back someday again with my book we
will catch up and I'll and I will see
you at chop talk if not before and I'll
be prepared with my vitamins as you say
yes get get plenty of rest before